Traveling northeast over the Ethiopian Highlands
Traveling over the Red Sea into the Arabian Peninsula
Heading northeast over the Arabian Peninsula
Over the Arabian Peninsula moving toward Iran
Over the Arabian Peninsula approaching Iran
Approaching the coast of Iran with the Zagros Mountains beyond
Over the Zagros Mountains in Iran
Over the Dasht-e Lut desert in Iran
Moving toward Turkmenistan and the Garagum desert
The Amu Darya River and the Pamir-Alay Mountains in central Asia
The Pamir-Alay Mountains and the Fergana Valley in central Asia
Heading into southeastern Kazakhstan from Kyrgyzstan
Traveling north over Kazakhstan
Over the Altai Mountains moving into Mongolia