Over the Pacific Ocean moving toward Baja California
Over Baja California looking north toward the United States
Over Mexico heading toward the southwest United States
Over the southwest United States
Over the Rocky Mountains approaching Denver
Traveling over the Great Plains of the United States
Approaching the Great Lakes with Ontario, Canada beyond
Over the Great Lakes approaching Ontario, Canada
The Aurora Borealis over western Ontario, Canada
The Aurora Borealis over northern Ontario, Canada
The Aurora Borealis over northern Quebec, Canada
Heading toward the North Atlantic with the Aurora Borealis over Labrador, Canada