Over the Pacific Ocean heading toward the United States
Traveling south down the coast of California
Over southern California moving toward Mexico
Approaching the Mojave Desert in southern California with Mexico beyond
The Gulf of California flanked by the Sonoran Desert and the Baja California Peninsula
The Sierra Madre Occidental mountains on the west coast of Mexico
Over the Sierra Madre Occidental mountains moving toward the west coast of Mexico
Looking south to the Pacific Ocean over the Sierra Madre del Sur in Mexico
The Pacific Ocean off the coast of Mexico
The Pacific Ocean off the coast of Mexico and Guatemala